{
    "subject": "Sandra_Goldbacher",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Me_Without_You__film_",
    "human_readable": "Sandra Goldbacher directed the film Me Without You.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8679252862930298,
            "question": "Who directed the film Me Without You?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8567401170730591,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Sandra Goldbacher."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8305288553237915,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Sandra Goldbacher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7098938822746277,
            "question": "Are there any other notable films directed by Sandra Goldbacher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5312379598617554,
            "question": "What is the plot of Me Without You?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5118780732154846,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Me Without You?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3969671428203583,
            "question": "When was Me Without You released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31105509400367737,
            "question": "What genre is Me Without You likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2811993658542633,
            "question": "How has Me Without You been received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21522217988967896,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did Me Without You receive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sandra Goldbacher directed the film Me Without You.",
            "html": "yago_14856_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Me Without You been received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "yago_14856_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Me Without You likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_14856_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Me Without You released?",
            "html": "yago_14856_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14856_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Sandra Goldbacher is the director of the film \"Me Without You,\" supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}